ACTWU's Organizing Department Records. 5619/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's Organizing Department Records
1960-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Organizing Department.
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Organizing Department.
5619/007
111.11 cubic feet
111 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of correspondence, reports, minutes of staff meetings, and files from the Organizing Department. Much of the material is related to the J. P. Stevens campaign.
6819665
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
July 2010
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 2011
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America And all other 5619 collections.
Clothing industry -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Textile industry -- United States; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Organizing Department; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
6819665
- Organizing Reports, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  January-December, 1980. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  January-December, 1979. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  January-December, 1978. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Yearly Reports, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  January-December, 1977. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing midyear and quarterly reports, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Organizing Reports, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  January-December, 1976. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  January-December, 1975. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  January-December, 1974. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  January-December, 1973. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  January-December, 1972. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  January-December, 1971. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Miscellaneous Data Concerning Organizing, 1965-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Progress, Successes, Summaries, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  January-December, 1982. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  January-December, 1983. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  January-December, 1981. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  January-December, 1984. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  June 1976­Dec. 1983. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Summaries of Organizing Trends, etc.
- Organizing Reports, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  January-December, 1985. Decertification, Recertification Elections, Progress, Success, % of elections won, etc.
- J. P. Stevens. IAM Reimbursement Staff Salary, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- J. P. Stevens. Insurance Case., 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- J. P. Stevens. I. L. G., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- J. P. Stevens: International Support (Box 2, Folder 4)
- J. P. Stevens - IUD Expenses, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- J. P. Stevens. I.U.D. Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Correspondence, 1978- 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- J. P. Stevens. IUD Reimbursements. Bills. Staff Salaries., 1969-1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- J. P. Stevens. IUD Reimbursements. Bills. Staff Salaries., 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens. IUD Reimbursements. Bills. Staff Salaries., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- J. P. Stevens. IUD Reimbursements. Bills. Staff Salaries., 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- J. P. Stevens. SI Kahn. Retainer and Correspondence., 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- J. P. Stevens: Kelso, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- J. P. Stevens. Legal Cases, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- J. P. Stevens. Leaflet Distributions, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- J. P. Stevens. Legal. J. P. Stevens Record is the Worst in the History of NLRB, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- J. P. Stevens. Legal., 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- J. P. Stevens. Legal., 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Americans Aroused by Stevens Law Violations (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Mailings to the Staff of J. P. Stevens. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Mailings to the Staff of J. P. Stevens. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Mailings to the Staff of J. P. Stevens., 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- J. P. Stevens. Material to take up with McIver and Coordinators, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- J. P. Stevens and Lowenstein. Pacific Mills Strike., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Columbia, S.C.
- J. P. Stevens: McIver Letters to the Staff, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- J. P. Stevens: Ed McConville, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- J. P. Stevens Leadership Meeting, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  November 29th. NYC. 15 Union Square. Board Room
- J. P. Stevens: Leaflets, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- J. P. Stevens: Crystal Lee Jordan, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- J. P. Stevens: Harold Mayer Productions, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- J. P. Stevens. Organizing Campaign, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- J. P. Stevens: Del Mileski, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- J. P. Stevens: Mailings to Outside Organizations, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- J. P. Stevens: Merger Convention ACTWU, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- J. P. Stevens: Foreign Operations, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Minneapolis City Council, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- J. P. Stevens: Negotiations, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- J. P. Stevens: Movie- White Horse, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- J. P. Stevens: NLRB, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- J. P. Stevens: N. C. Council of Churches, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens: NAACP, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- J. P. Stevens: National Urban League, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- J. P. Stevens: Newsletters, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- J. P. Stevens: New England Plants, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- J. P. Stevens: New Milford Plant, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- J. P. Stevens: Norma Rae, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- J. P. Stevens: Orientation Kits, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- J. P. Stevens: Other Unions, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Reports on J. P. Stevens Organizing (Box 3, Folder 18)
- J. P. Stevens: Publicity, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- J. P. Stevens: Publicity, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- J. P. Stevens: Policy Meeting, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- J. P. Stevens: Political, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- J. P. Stevens: Photographs from Rally (Box 3, Folder 23)
- J. P. Stevens: Pension Plan, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- J. P. Stevens: Plant Survey, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- J. P. Stevens: U.S. and Foreign Plant Lists, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Publicity, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- J. P. Stevens: News Releases, 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Program to help J. P. Stevens Workers Organize, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- J. P. Stevens and Philip W. Moore, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- J. P. Stevens: Printing Plants, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- J. P. Stevens: Products, Brands and Shipments, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- J. P. Stevens: Press List (Box 3, Folder 33)
- J. P. Stevens: Profit Sharing Court Suit, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- J. P. Stevens: Product Competitors, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- J. P. Stevens: Questionnaires, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- J. P. Stevens: Questionnaires, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  Completed Stories
- Boycott End. Lists and Texts, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- ACTWU. Support. Boycott Papers, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- International, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Endorsements of J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Resolutions: Religious, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Resolutions: Civil Rights, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Resolutions: Students and Academic, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Resolutions: Women, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Resolutions: Elected Officials, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Resolutions: Political Org., 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Resolutions: City Councils and State & County Legislatures, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Resolutions: Senior Citizens, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Resolutions: Labor, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Church Problems. Stevens Expansion, 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Abraham and Straus, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Allied, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Associated Stores in Various States, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Bloomingdale's (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Federated, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Gimbels, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- May CO., 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- J. C.Penney, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Sears, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Woolworth/Woolco, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Carpets, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Fabric Stores, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Schedules for Workers, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Stevens Research, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Social Justice, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- State Feds., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Southerners for Economic Justice (SEJ), 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Stevens Workers, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Term Papered Studies. The J. P. Stevens Boycott: Is it having an effect?, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Staff Mailings, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Staff Mailings, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Staff Mailings, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Students, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Staff Mailings, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- T Shirt Orders, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Trade Shows J. P. S., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- J. P. S. Stockholders Meeting, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Thank yous, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- J. P. S.: UAW, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- United Farm Workers (UFW), 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Women's Auxiliaries, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- WES WELLS, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Dayton, OH
- Local and Joint Board Program, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Malizia Report, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Media, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Meetings: Other than Staff, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Leadership Conference, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  June 9-12th
- Staff Meeting, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Philadelphia. April 8-11th
- Staff Meeting, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Ottawa. October.
- Staff Meeting, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  New York. October 3-4th
- Staff Meeting, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Atlanta. May 22-23rd
- Staff Meeting, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  New York. May10-11th
- Staff Meeting, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Chicago. May 1-2nd
- Staff Meetings, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  St. Louis. September26-27th. Chicago. September 29-30th. New York. October 3-4th
- Staff Meeting, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Chicago. September 29-30th
- Staff Meetings, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  New York. March 16th. Chicago. March 18-19th
- Staff Meeting, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  September 26-17th
- Staff Meeting. JPS, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Staff Meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Chicago
- Staff Meeting, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Chicago. November 15-16th
- Employee Spying, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- ACTWU. Express Mail Customer Receipts (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Media Information Kit, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Mintzer, Trostler and Rothchild, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Nation's Labor. J. P. Stevens, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Advertising Correspondence, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- MTR Bills, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Media Schedule, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- New York and State Campaigns, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- J. P. Stevens. NAACP, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Norma Rae, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- J. P. Stevens: NLRB, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Ohio Public Interest Campaign (OPIC), 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Organizing, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Organizing, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- J. P. Stevens: Plants, Labels, Location products, RN#, and Brand Names, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Press Release, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Press Releases, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Press Releases, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Press Releases, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Press Releases, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Program and Calender, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Propaganda, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Propaganda. Straightening Things Out, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Publicity, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Publicity. C. H. A. O. S. Committee to help the Amalgamated Organize Stevens (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Publicity, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Health/ Safety, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- PX Purchases. J. P. S., 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Stanley Ruttenberg, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Survey Boycott of the J. P. S. Company's Products, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Tabular Reports. Summary. Supplemental Report
- Radio, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Radical, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Financial Campaign, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- J. P. Stevens: Frontlash, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- J. P. Stevens: Frontlash, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- J. P. Stevens: Frontlash, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Fruit of the Loom, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- J. P. Stevens: Governments Contracts, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- GEB- Report, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Hotel Campaign, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- J. P. Stevens: Hotels, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- House Subcommittee, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- International Ford Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- International Ford Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Institutions, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- International: Belgium, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- International: Japan, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- J. P. Stevens International: Misc., 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- J. P. Stevens International: Misc., 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- International Misc., 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- International: Australia, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- International Christophersen Correspondence. J. P. Stevens., 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Si Kahn, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- International ACTWU Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- J. P. Stevens. International Meeting., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  Washington
- International: France, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- J. P. Stevens: Canada, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- International: England, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- International OECD. J. P. Stevens., 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- J. P. Stevens. Gimbels, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- JLC, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- J. P. Stevens: Joint Boards, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- History of JPS Campaign, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- King Center, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Klepper Associates, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- ACTWU. Klepper. Interview Schedule, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- JPS. Labor Day, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Legal Approval, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Legal Approval, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Legal Approval, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Legal Approval, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Social Justice- Legal Approval, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Legal General, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Legal General, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Legal: Court Decisions. JPS, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Legal: Court Decisions. JPS, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Legal: Court Decisions. JPS, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Court Decisions, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- ACTWU Court Decisions, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Legal, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Legal, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Legal Pending, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- JPS. A. Philip Randolph, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Staff List. Purchases. Committees, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Status/Activities Report, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  7/76-10/77
- Activities Report- TWVA, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  11/75-4/76
- JPS. AFL-CIO, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- ACTWU. T he Struggle for Economic Justice at JPS, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Activities/Status Reports. JPS, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Activities/Status Reports. JPS, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Activities/Status Reports. JPS, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Activities/Status Reports. JPS, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Ads ACTWU, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Ads. ACTWU, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Ads. ACTWU, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Ads (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Ads. ACTWU. J. P. S., 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Materials put together for JPS book to AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO. Sub-Committee Boycotts, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- American Arbitration Association, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Americans for Democratic Action (ADA), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Big Mama, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Campaign Guide, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- JPS. Brown Lung Association, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- JPS. Campaign Proposals, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Cancellations. JPS., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Cancellations. JPS., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Citizen's Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Stevens Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Clergy, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)